(Sheldon:)But I'm going to take a stab here.
You're either sad or nauseated.
(Raj:)-I'm sad.
-I was going to say sad.
(Sheldon:)I don't know why I hedged.
(Raj:)What are you eating?
(Sheldon:)Elbow macaroni with ground hamburger
and tomato sauce.
(Raj:)Oh, beefaroni.
(Raj:)I think I'll miss you most of all.
(Leonard:)I've always been a little confused
about this. Why don't Hindus eat beef?
(Raj:)-We believe cows are gods.
-Not technically.
(Sheldon:)In Hinduism,
cattle are thought to be like God.
Do not tell me about my culture.
I'll take you out, I swear to cow.
(Sheldon:)I'm sorry.
(Raj:)Me too. I'm just-- I'm a little on edge.
Mm, understandable. Your life seems
to be crumbling around you...
(Sheldon:)...and your future appears bleak at best.
(Raj:)Thank you.
(Sheldon:)And you're wrong
about Hinduism and cows.
Hey, Raj, Professor Laughlin
is looking for someone to join...
(Howard(arriving):)-...the stellar evolution research team.
-You're kidding. That's fantastic.